Hunted by your future, haunted by your past.
Looper is a action, thriller, science fiction film directed by Rian Johnson.
In the year 2044, time travel has not yet been
invented but in 30 years it will have been.
When the mob wants to get rid of someone, they will send their target into the
past where a looper, a hired gun, like Joe is waiting to mop up.
Joe is getting rich and life is good until the day the mob decides to close
the loop, sending back Joe's future self for assassination.
Joe, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Old Joe, played by Bruce Willis.
Sara, played by Emily Blunt.
Seth, played by Paul Dano.
Kid Blue, played by Noah Segan.
Suzie, played by Piper Perabo.
Looper is a 2012 American science fiction action thriller film written and
directed by Rian Johnson, and produced by Ram Bergman and James D.
It stars Bruce Willis, Joseph Gordon-Levitt, and Emily Blunt.
It revolves around "present-day" contract killers called "loopers" whose targets
are sent back through time by criminal syndicates from the future.
Looper was selected as the opening film of the 2012 Toronto International Film Festival and was released in the
United States on September 28, 2012, by a partnership between TriStar Pictures and FilmDistrict.
The film  received critical acclaim and was a box office success,
grossing $176 million worldwide on a $30 million budget.
The film explores themes of future, suicide, assassin, dystopia, drug addiction.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.